Hime
Where did she go?
ano ittousei no sanzameku hikari de
Under the eerie light of the first star
“You know, I want to be like a sun”
anata to dansu o odorou ka
Let's dance a dance together
waga taiyoukei no kodou ni awasete
To the heartbeat of our solar system
“You can be a sun, Hime”
karamatta suteppu de kirameite, sei!
Shine with entwined steps, Star!
Bellybutton girl
Hina Suzuki
Nayutan Seijin - Solar System Disco
Giggling girl
Hime Tanaka
Ranbada rumba the two of us rendezvous in space
ranbada runba futari sora de randebuu na
mou, wazuratte renya nemurenai
I suffer every night and can't sleep
seiza ni natte mazaru donna ittousei mo
No planet that mixes into a constellation
anata ni kawaru koudo wa nai wa
Can shine as your replacement
kousha no ura ano hi anata mitsuketa
That day I found you behind the school building
kiseki sae ima mo hanarenai
Not even a miracle will leave now
tonari ni shigeku mieru meiousei mo
Even Pluto that haunts my view
ainiku, ima wa kyoumi ga nai wa
Unfortunately, I have no interest in now
hoshi ga macchatte
Stars floated
mune ga nacchatte
My chest beat loudly
kidzukeba kanata
When I realize I was already beyond
ano ittousei no sanzameku hikari de
Under the eerie light of the first star
anata to dansu o odorou ka
Let's dance a dance together
waga taiyoukei no housoku ni sasoware
Invited by our solar system's rules
majiwatta kando de kirameite, sei!
Shine with mixed brightness, Star!
oo o oo! seikansen o tsunaide
Oh, oh, oh! Connect the star lines
oo o oo! anata ni todoke
Oh, oh, oh! Deliver to you
oo o oo! uchuu no hate kara
Oh, oh, oh! From the ends of space
oo o oo! anata shinkoukei!
Oh, oh, oh! You're an invasion system!
daitai no dansu wa hoshi ga hikari shirube to naru no sa
For most dances starlight becomes a standard
mitaiken na suteppu de HA, HA, HA, HA
With inexperienced steps HA, HA, HA, HA
daitan na sutansu de shuukai kidou jou nazoru no sa
With a bold stance trace the path of orbit
taiyoukei no desuko de HA, HA, HA, HA
With the solar system disco HA, HA, HA, HA
chuu tayutatte itsuka futari wasureru
Floating away in space, we will someday forget
kotoba sae ima wa motometai
Those words I seek now
choushinsei o negau kureta sekai mo
This dimmed world that wishes for a supernova
fushigi to ima wa dou demo ii wa
Strangely I don't care at all now
aa nan mo naku tatte
Ah, even without anything
nantonaku datte
Somehow still
hoshi wa megutte
Stars orbitー
ano ittousei no todokanu hikari wa
The first star's light that is impossible to reach
haruka na kanata de kirameita
Shined far beyond
waga taiyoukei no housoku mo hazurete
Even outside our solar system's rules
“sore demo ii sa” te o nobashite!
“But that's okay” I stretch out my arms!
saa, ikuseisou to yadoshita omoi de
Your weight and stored memories
anata no subete motomeyou ka
I'll seek your everything
nee, nan kounen no koudai na tabiji de
Yeah, on a vast journey of many light years
hiku no renri o sagasou ka
Let's look for comparative love affairs
ano ittousei no sanzameku hikari de
Under the eerie light of the first star
anata to dansu o odorou ka
Let's dance a dance together
hora suikin datte chi ka moku do ten kai mo
Come on, even all the elements
futari no ginga de kirameita, sei!
Shined in our galaxy, Star!
oo o oo! seikansen o tsunaide
Oh, oh, oh! Connect the star lines
oo o oo! anata ni todoke
Oh, oh, oh! Deliver to you
oo o oo! uchuu no hate kara
Oh, oh, oh! From the end of space
oo o oo! anata shinkoukei!
Oh, oh, oh! You're an invasion system!
Aah, this is nice