Innocent girl mode
We should avoid places with too many people
Right? We'd get killed instantly
Then let's go to the corner of the map
Let's try to survive until the end, guys
Alright, go
Hina-chan, can you mute your mic for a second?
Done
Inspector Suzuki!
Detective mode
Veteran detective
Hime Tanaka
Newbie detective
Hina Suzuki
Infiltrating
Yeah, what's up?
Look at our beautiful tandem drop
We've become one
We look like flying squirrels
Our performance is a sight to behold
Also, can I say one thing?
Yes?
We're heading to the wrong place
Undercover Cops
Mission
Go undercover in Knives Out
Don't let anyone find out you're a cop
Innocent girl mode
Hello
Hi
Infiltrating...
Pleased to meet you
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you too
Do you play this game a lot?
What?
Do you often play Knives Out?
Nah. I'm terrible at it
Don't worry, we're playing it for the first time
Yeah
HimeHina wiki
Playing the game for the first time on recording day
Us No. 1 and 2 are friends, actually
HimeHina wiki
Acting like two girls just having fun
Looking forward to playing with you
Just so you know
I really, really suck
Well... We suck at least as much
Getting competitive at sucking
Detective mode
We're heading to the wrong place
Senpaai!
We're heading for the wrong place!
I'm not even close
I'm gonna talk to him
I'm so sorry. We botched our jump
Innocent girl mode
Is there anyone around?
Lemme know if you see an enemy
Okay
Will do
Sounds like a fun guy
Inspector Suzuki!
Detective mode
What is it?
Huh? Where'd 1 and 2 go?
Nr. 1
Nr. 2
Innocent girl mode
Sorry
We're still here
I think we landed miles away from the center
Really?!
Huh? Me too
We're scattered across the map
Oh, oh dear
We're reeeaaally far away
HimeHina wiki
About as far from the safe zone as they can be
Innocent girl mode
Detective mode
Inspector Suzuki!
Can I say something, inspector Suzuki?
What is it?
Wait, I mean “detective”
What is it, detective Tanaka?
Just one thing
Our acting is all over the place
HimeHina wiki
Switching between personalities gets confusing
Right. We need to concentrate!
Yes, we're on a missh, on a misshionnm
Pull yourself together!
Oh crap
He's saying something
Aye've only found a helmet so far
Just a helmet!
Cute
Must be a little girl from Kansai
Wait, not a girl
Innocent girl mode
Are you from Kansai?
I am
Hey, Magi
Talking to No. 3 as well
Are you a piece of trash?
Magi @ Trash
I hear a car coming
Are they coming to pick us up?
That's so nice! Thank you!
Awesome!
Wait
You can't get in
Oh, it's full
Already full
Two-seater...
Wow! Living up to his name
At least he came over to us
Yes, thank you
Detective mode
Detective Suzuki!
Detective Suzuki, we have...
...some really friendly guys on our team!
You're right, they are
That Kansai girl and that... trash girl are fantastic
The Kansai one is so kind
This infiltration is going great
We're completely undercover
Yes, no one is noticing our true identity
Oh, gunshots
Apparently he heard shooting
Shooting
Innocent girl mode
Are they shooting? (Completely different)
Gunshots?
Over there
Where?
Where could they be?
Oh, found one. Enemy spotted
An enemy!
Where is he?
Tanaka sprinting in the opposite direction
Let's follow him
Suzuki firing by accident
Whoops, wrong button
Are the others nearby?
Found 'em!
Tanaka corrects her course as a result
Where?
I heard a gunshot
Where are they...
Oh, they're shooting
That looks bad!
He got him
He's taking hits
Wait, he did? Wow
I got him...
Awesome!
You're good at this
How's your health?
I gawt him!
Whooo!
Cute
You gawt him!
Amazing
Innocent girl mode
Ah, found one
Ow! I got shot!
Where are you?
HimeHina wiki
Controls are super hard
Oww...
I think you're close
Innocent girl mode
Oooow I died
Whoa, that scared me
Detective Tanaka KIA
You died?!
Detective mode
Detective Suzuki
Detective Suzuki!
What?
I'm watching you from heaven
Sooner or la-
Sooner or later, your time comes to an end
That's how it goes in life!
Having another go
Where's the safe zone...?
Oh, we're already in it
I'll talk to them
Go ahead
We're in the safe zone, aren't we
Innocent girl mode
Nice, isn't it?
Detective mode
They ignored me
No response
I'm get the impression they find me annoying
Maybe they realized we're undercover cops?
That's bad!
I almost forgot our objective
I just wanted to talk in a cute voice and get pampered
Truly playing like a Hime
(※ “Hime” = “Princess” = Girl getting free stuff in MMOs)
Do you have a backpack?
Yup, got one
Good
Huh? What?
Oops, my bad
Sorry
Already I'm shooting by accident
Shouldn't you tell them it wasn't on purpose?
Make sure it sounds cute. “Oops, my bad～”
(※ Tara-chan from the anime Sazae-san)
I'd rather die
Feeling rebellious, detective Suzuki?!
Did the suspects make a run for it?
They must be scared of us, right?
It's just as I thought!
We're simply too powerful
They're probably running for their lives
First they ran from us in PUBG
And now in Knives Out!
I cannot believe how little resistance they put up!
We could take over this world with the snap of a finger!
Next thing you know you'll get shot
For a second there I was scared my mic was still on
“With the snap of a finger!”
That would've jeopardized the mission
Yeah, no kidding
Missed him completely...
We're in a pickle, Suzuki!
The enemy is too strong!
We have a situation, alright
Need some healing items, senpai?
Innocent girl mode
This is it, right?
Aah, thank you so much～
Thank you...
Wait, my mic...
My mic has been on this whole time
Suzuki! Get your act together!
Detective mode
Turn off your mic
It's fine, they're probably ignoring us anyway
Detective Suzuki
What is it, senpai?
Detective Suzuki, I feel so calm in this mode
I feel comfortable
I know what you mean
It feels like coming home
NOOOOOooooo
THIRD PLACE!
Sorry. Third place?
That's terrible
I guess the knives really are out in Knives Out
Tantaranta tantaranta sub-scri-be!
Tanaka and Suzuki
Sub-scri-be!
Aw yeah!