Hated by life itself
Cocoa Domyoji
“shinitai nante iu na yo
“Don’t you wish for death when you’re feeling weak!”
akiramenaide ikiro yo”
“Hardships aren’t as hard as they seem to be!”
sonna uta ga tadashii nante
Sure, say that all you want, you’re not fooling me
bakageteru yo na
with those words you never mean
jissai jibun wa shinde mo yokute
While I don’t care to die, I don’t mind a bit
mawari ga shindara kanashikute
But someone I love? God, I think I’d wish I did
“sore ga iya dakara” tte iu
I suppose “Because I won’t like it”
ego nan desu
is all my ego is
tanin ga ikite mo dou demo yokute
Happy to gaze upon the pain of the haven’t-met
dareka o kirau koto mo fasshon de
Cowering in our hatred has become a fashion trend
soredemo “heiwa ni ikiyou” nante
Even so, we’re supposed to “live a peaceful life”?
suteki na koto deshou
Even though I bet it’s nice, I bet we’ve tried
gamen no saki de wa dareka ga shinde
Someone succumbs behind the colors of the monitor
sore o nageite dareka ga utatte
Deep in grief, another weeps by singing in their honor
sore ni kanka sareta shounen ga
Hearing that song, a humming young boy wandered
naifu o motte hashitta
off with a knife and an offer
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Everybody hated well by life itself, we’ll never know
kachikan mo ego mo oshitsukete
why they force code and ego on the radio
itsumo dareka o koroshitai uta o
Day-to-day, they’re singing out “I’ll take you down”, but then again,
kantan ni denpa de nagashita
who takes when they’re really being generous?
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Everybody hated well by life itself, we’ll never know
karugarushiku shinitai datoka
why “I want to die” is treated like another joke
karugarushiku inochi o miteru
That world where we see the worth in growing old
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Anybody hated well by life itself will never know
Life
okane ga nai no de kyou mo
Penniless again, through the day anew
ichinichijuu damin o ouka suru
I decide to praise the lazy and sing out of tune
ikiru imi nante midasezu
Lost upon life’s meaning, I take in the truth
muda o jikaku shite iki o suru
Breathe and see there isn’t anything I’m meant to do
sabishii nante kotoba de
Would these wounds be better off expressed
kono kizu ga arawasete ii mono ka
with the lowly illustration “I’m so lonely” suggests?
sonna iji bakari kakae
Shouldering nothing but this stubbornness,
kyou mo hitori beddo ni nemuru
I’m nothing but alone when I go to bed
shounen datta bokutachi wa
Kids with passion to play make-believe will
itsuka seinen ni kawatteiku
become young adults with a will to achieve
toshioite itsuka kareha no you ni
As we age, there comes a day we fester like a falling leaf,
dare ni mo shirarezu kuchite iku
carried down without a clue to prove we ever breathed...
fujimi no karada o te ni irete
Breathing on for centuries in a deathless design
isshou shinazu ni ikite iku
Bored for eternity, the only to survive...
sonna SF o mousou shiteru
These are the kinds of sci-fi dreams always on my mind
jibun ga shinde mo dou demo yokute
Numb to the pain, can I die? Though I’m not afraid
soredemo mawari ni ikite hoshikute
All the same, I have to pay attention to the hearts I’d break
mujun o kakaete ikiteku nante
Lost in conflicting thoughts, I’m sure they’d have a lot to say
okorarete shimau
Yes, I can guess what they’d convey:
“tadashii mono wa tadashiku inasai”
“Perfect things need to stay as perfect as they always were”
“shinitakunai nara ikite inasai”
“If you can’t confront demise, then live the life you don’t deserve”
kanashiku naru nara soredemo ii nara
Since we’re bound to end up sad and back to being hurt,
zutto hitori de warae yo
we should laugh with the friends we lack forever
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Everybody hated well by life itself, we’ll never know
koufuku no imi sura wakarazu
why we claim to get the happiness we haven’t shown
umareta kankyou bakari nikunde
Angered by our past hands, past, as we complain aloud
kantan ni kako bakari norou
We smile while pretending that we’re better now
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Everybody hated well by life itself, we’ll never know
sayonara bakari ga sukisugite
why “So long” took on the meaning of “I wanna go”
hontou no wakare nado shiranai
That time where “Goodbye” implied “For now, I hope”
bokura wa inochi ni kirawarete iru
Anybody hated well by life itself will never know
koufuku mo
Contentment
wakare mo
and exits
aijou mo
affection
yuujou mo
and friendships
They’re gifts you can get for your money
kokkei na yume no tawamure de
zenbu kane de kaeru shiromono
Within but a whimsical fantasy
ashita shinde shimau kamo shirenai
I could be dead tomorrow, yet I’m sure in some way,
subete muda ni naru kamo shirenai
when I go, I’ll get to know my life was such a waste
asa mo
Through daylight
yoru mo
and stardom
haru mo
through springtime
aki mo
and autumn
kawarazu dareka ga doko ka de shinu
we die everyday, and that’s exactly why I chase
yume mo asu mo nani mo iranai
no wishes or visions; since all I can afford
kimi ga ikite ita nara sore de ii
is protecting your life, I ask for that and nothing more
sou da. hontou wa
Of course... That’s surely
sou iu koto ga utaitai
all I’ll ever need to sing for
inochi ni kirawarete iru
Hated well by life itself, we’ll never know
kekkyoku itsuka wa shinde iku
what makes the meaning matter when we die alone
kimi datte boku datte
It’ll taint you, it’ll taint two
itsuka wa kareha no you ni kuchiteku
Soon enough, the rest of us will sink like a leaf into
soredemo bokura wa hisshi ni ikite
Anywhere we know it’s not for naught, ‘cause we don’t stop
inochi o hisshi ni kakaete ikite
Going out and off, always giving everything we got
koroshite
To killing,
agaite
to kicking,
waratte
to grinning,
kakaete
to gritting
ikite
Living
IKIRO
Living on!
Cocoa Music
Hated by life itself